[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "CC", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What made you do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, like I said today, Piers, is that I wanted to be able to put a face and a voice to those women out there that didn't want to or could not, for whatever their reasons are -- I wanted to speak about this because it was -- I wanted to tell the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "I", "said", "today", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "that", "I", "wanted", "to", "be", "able", "to", "put", "a", "face", "and", "a", "voice", "to", "those", "women", "out", "there", "that", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "or", "could", "not", ",", "for", "whatever", "their", "reasons", "are", "--", "I", "wanted", "to", "speak", "about", "this", "because", "it", "was", "--", "I", "wanted", "to", "tell", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994", "1997"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Educational Foundation of the National Restaurant Association"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ":", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "When did you first meet Herman Cain?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "first", "meet", "Herman", "Cain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I first met Herman in 1994 -- 1997 when I was employed at the Educational Foundation of the National Restaurant Association.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "first", "met", "Herman", "in", "1994", "--", "1997", "when", "I", "was", "employed", "at", "the", "Educational", "Foundation", "of", "the", "National", "Restaurant", "Association", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "And then you were laid off, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "you", "were", "laid", "off", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yes, I was terminated.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "was", "terminated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And you then made contact with Herman Cain?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "then", "made", "contact", "with", "Herman", "Cain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Herman's"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "And whose idea was it to have dinner?", "question_tokens": ["And", "whose", "idea", "was", "it", "to", "have", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "That was Herman's.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "Herman", "'s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "And did you drink alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "you", "drink", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I had a glass of wine, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "glass", "of", "wine", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "And did Mr. Cain drink?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "Mr.", "Cain", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, how much did you have together?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "much", "did", "you", "have", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I -- you know, I really can't remember.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "really", "ca", "n't", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Was he a gentleman during dinner?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "a", "gentleman", "during", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Did he say then that he would be able to help you perhaps get your job back?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "say", "then", "that", "he", "would", "be", "able", "to", "help", "you", "perhaps", "get", "your", "job", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "He -- not so much during dinner, but he said that he would look into it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "not", "so", "much", "during", "dinner", ",", "but", "he", "said", "that", "he", "would", "look", "into", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "And whose idea was it to then get in the car together?", "question_tokens": ["And", "whose", "idea", "was", "it", "to", "then", "get", "in", "the", "car", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, it was his because I had to get a ride back to the hotel because I didn't have the car.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "his", "because", "I", "had", "to", "get", "a", "ride", "back", "to", "the", "hotel", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "have", "the", "car", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Were you shocked by what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "shocked", "by", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Very, very much so because, first of all, he had met my boyfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", ",", "very", "much", "so", "because", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "had", "met", "my", "boyfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Are you concerned about the impact of all this on your child?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "the", "impact", "of", "all", "this", "on", "your", "child", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Have you at any stage in the last 14 years made any approach to Herman Cain to get some kind of apology from him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "at", "any", "stage", "in", "the", "last", "14", "years", "made", "any", "approach", "to", "Herman", "Cain", "to", "get", "some", "kind", "of", "apology", "from", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 14 years"], "PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Was he aware that he had gone too far, if what you say is true?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "aware", "that", "he", "had", "gone", "too", "far", ",", "if", "what", "you", "say", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, when you tell someone, you know, this is not why I'm here, please drive me back, and I was very stern and, yes, he knew -- I wouldn't say he was apologetic, but he knew I wasn't happy about what went on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "tell", "someone", ",", "you", "know", ",", "this", "is", "not", "why", "I", "'m", "here", ",", "please", "drive", "me", "back", ",", "and", "I", "was", "very", "stern", "and", ",", "yes", ",", "he", "knew", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "he", "was", "apologetic", ",", "but", "he", "knew", "I", "was", "n't", "happy", "about", "what", "went", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How many other people have known about what happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "other", "people", "have", "known", "about", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "I only told two people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "only", "told", "two", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "And who are they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "We're not going to name them, Piers, but we are identifying them as we did today as a physician that she was dating who has provided a declaration under penalty of perjury to us, which we have signed.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "name", "them", ",", "Piers", ",", "but", "we", "are", "identifying", "them", "as", "we", "did", "today", "as", "a", "physician", "that", "she", "was", "dating", "who", "has", "provided", "a", "declaration", "under", "penalty", "of", "perjury", "to", "us", ",", "which", "we", "have", "signed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["hundreds of millions of dollars"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "JJS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "How do you counter that charge?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "counter", "that", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, they didn't describe me the way most people would describe me, which is a women's rights attorney, which I have been for 36 years and we've done more sexual harassment cases in our law firm, in our private law firm, than any other law firm in the country, and won literally hundreds of millions of dollars for victims of sexual harassment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "did", "n't", "describe", "me", "the", "way", "most", "people", "would", "describe", "me", ",", "which", "is", "a", "women", "'s", "rights", "attorney", ",", "which", "I", "have", "been", "for", "36", "years", "and", "we", "'ve", "done", "more", "sexual", "harassment", "cases", "in", "our", "law", "firm", ",", "in", "our", "private", "law", "firm", ",", "than", "any", "other", "law", "firm", "in", "the", "country", ",", "and", "won", "literally", "hundreds", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", "for", "victims", "of", "sexual", "harassment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Sharon, let me ask you, did you believe that Herman Cain should now stand down as a candidate for the Republican Party nomination?", "question_tokens": ["Sharon", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "did", "you", "believe", "that", "Herman", "Cain", "should", "now", "stand", "down", "as", "a", "candidate", "for", "the", "Republican", "Party", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I believe -- up until this point, I believe that he first needs to apologize and he needs to admit it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "--", "up", "until", "this", "point", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "he", "first", "needs", "to", "apologize", "and", "he", "needs", "to", "admit", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Sharon, let me ask you, how did your boyfriend react when you told him at the time what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["Sharon", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "how", "did", "your", "boyfriend", "react", "when", "you", "told", "him", "at", "the", "time", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "He tried to ask me more details, and I said I really don't want to talk about it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "tried", "to", "ask", "me", "more", "details", ",", "and", "I", "said", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "How is this affecting you emotionally?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "this", "affecting", "you", "emotionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "To be honest with you, right now I haven't even watched any of the media.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "be", "honest", "with", "you", ",", "right", "now", "I", "have", "n't", "even", "watched", "any", "of", "the", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Are you considering filing charges against him?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "considering", "filing", "charges", "against", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, first of all, I believe the statute of limitations would have run out by now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "believe", "the", "statute", "of", "limitations", "would", "have", "run", "out", "by", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "My final question to you, Sharon, is simply, do you think that Herman Cain should become president of the United States?", "question_tokens": ["My", "final", "question", "to", "you", ",", "Sharon", ",", "is", "simply", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "Herman", "Cain", "should", "become", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "I don't think we can have anyone in the White House who is unable to tell the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "can", "have", "anyone", "in", "the", "White", "House", "who", "is", "unable", "to", "tell", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon", "United States"], "PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Were you surprised by the verdict in the end?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "the", "verdict", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Not surprised, Piers, especially when you take into consideration the amount of time that the jury deliberated.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "surprised", ",", "Piers", ",", "especially", "when", "you", "take", "into", "consideration", "the", "amount", "of", "time", "that", "the", "jury", "deliberated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Was that from members of his family?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "from", "members", "of", "his", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Yes, it was from right behind me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "from", "right", "behind", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What are you anticipating will be the outcome here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "anticipating", "will", "be", "the", "outcome", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "OWLANDS: Well, his medical license in each of the states where he practices will have to be dealt with by those medical board.", "answer_tokens": ["OWLANDS", ":", "Well", ",", "his", "medical", "license", "in", "each", "of", "the", "states", "where", "he", "practices", "will", "have", "to", "be", "dealt", "with", "by", "those", "medical", "board", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "went", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, you know, I think what went wrong was a lot of the pretrial rulings that were made by the court in reference to some of the evidence that we planned to offer for the jury to consider.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "what", "went", "wrong", "was", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "pretrial", "rulings", "that", "were", "made", "by", "the", "court", "in", "reference", "to", "some", "of", "the", "evidence", "that", "we", "planned", "to", "offer", "for", "the", "jury", "to", "consider", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "And how did Dr. Murray react after he realized that he had been found guilty of effectively killing Michael Jackson, one of the most iconic entertainers of our lifetime?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "did", "Dr.", "Murray", "react", "after", "he", "realized", "that", "he", "had", "been", "found", "guilty", "of", "effectively", "killing", "Michael", "Jackson", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "iconic", "entertainers", "of", "our", "lifetime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Well, he was clearly devastated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "clearly", "devastated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Where is Dr. Murray tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "Dr.", "Murray", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Dr. Murray is currently at the Inmate Reception Center where he's being -- going through the booking process.", "answer_tokens": ["Dr.", "Murray", "is", "currently", "at", "the", "Inmate", "Reception", "Center", "where", "he", "'s", "being", "--", "going", "through", "the", "booking", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "What do you think would be a fair punishment given that he's been convicted?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "would", "be", "a", "fair", "punishment", "given", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "convicted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["June 25th of 2009"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Dr. Murray", "Mr. Jackson"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "I mean, you would have been uneasy as a lawyer about that situation, that state of affairs, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "would", "have", "been", "uneasy", "as", "a", "lawyer", "about", "that", "situation", ",", "that", "state", "of", "affairs", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, Piers, we have to remember what happened here on June 25th of 2009, Dr. Murray did not have Mr. Jackson on a drip.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "we", "have", "to", "remember", "what", "happened", "here", "on", "June", "25th", "of", "2009", ",", "Dr.", "Murray", "did", "not", "have", "Mr.", "Jackson", "on", "a", "drip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Excuse me, would we be appealing?", "question_tokens": ["Excuse", "me", ",", "would", "we", "be", "appealing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Are you concerned about his mental condition?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "his", "mental", "condition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "I'm not concerned about his mental condition.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "concerned", "about", "his", "mental", "condition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Right verdict, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "verdict", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, the verdict was certainly reasonable verdict.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "verdict", "was", "certainly", "reasonable", "verdict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "And why wasn't he ready to argue that bail motion more effectively?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "was", "n't", "he", "ready", "to", "argue", "that", "bail", "motion", "more", "effectively", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RBR", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "It did seem extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "did", "seem", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Looking back, do you have any regrets now about the way the jury composition was made up?", "question_tokens": ["Looking", "back", ",", "do", "you", "have", "any", "regrets", "now", "about", "the", "way", "the", "jury", "composition", "was", "made", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Would you think that would be an appropriate sentence given that he's been convicted?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "think", "that", "would", "be", "an", "appropriate", "sentence", "given", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "convicted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, I hope the lawyers do a better job on sentencing than they did on bail.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "the", "lawyers", "do", "a", "better", "job", "on", "sentencing", "than", "they", "did", "on", "bail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you think she has credibility?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "has", "credibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "It was a great interview, by the way.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "great", "interview", ",", "by", "the", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "How do you feel now that this doctor that you had so much time for and support for has been convicted of the death of Michael Jackson?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "now", "that", "this", "doctor", "that", "you", "had", "so", "much", "time", "for", "and", "support", "for", "has", "been", "convicted", "of", "the", "death", "of", "Michael", "Jackson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "In the words, piers, of a famous actor, I'm mad as hell, and I ain't going to take it any more.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "words", ",", "piers", ",", "of", "a", "famous", "actor", ",", "I", "'m", "mad", "as", "hell", ",", "and", "I", "ai", "n't", "going", "to", "take", "it", "any", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Do you think that Conrad Murray has been stitched up here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "Conrad", "Murray", "has", "been", "stitched", "up", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Conrad Murray was the only man on this planet that loved Michael Jackson enough to try to help him.", "answer_tokens": ["Conrad", "Murray", "was", "the", "only", "man", "on", "this", "planet", "that", "loved", "Michael", "Jackson", "enough", "to", "try", "to", "help", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Where the hell were they when he was shooting himself with Demerol?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "the", "hell", "were", "they", "when", "he", "was", "shooting", "himself", "with", "Demerol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "You're clearly feeling very emotional about Dennis.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "clearly", "feeling", "very", "emotional", "about", "Dennis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Have you had the chance to talk to Conrad Murray?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "Conrad", "Murray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Just when I testified.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "when", "I", "testified", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "I mean, if you had the chance now, what would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "now", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "How did you feel when you saw that Conrad Murray had been convicted?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "saw", "that", "Conrad", "Murray", "had", "been", "convicted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "I was happy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "From your belief, from what you read and heard, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "belief", ",", "from", "what", "you", "read", "and", "heard", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, one, when I read -- did my testimony and my report, I just reviewed Dr. Murray's very own words to investigation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", ",", "when", "I", "read", "--", "did", "my", "testimony", "and", "my", "report", ",", "I", "just", "reviewed", "Dr.", "Murray", "'s", "very", "own", "words", "to", "investigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Or will it still carry on but just in a discreet way?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "will", "it", "still", "carry", "on", "but", "just", "in", "a", "discreet", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "No, I think hopefully it is over.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "hopefully", "it", "is", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What was your reaction to the verdict today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "verdict", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, I was happy in some regards, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "happy", "in", "some", "regards", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "I also want to ask you, as I would ask anyone I guess involved in this, do you have any sympathy with Conrad Murray, who has always said he was just trying to help Michael?", "question_tokens": ["I", "also", "want", "to", "ask", "you", ",", "as", "I", "would", "ask", "anyone", "I", "guess", "involved", "in", "this", ",", "do", "you", "have", "any", "sympathy", "with", "Conrad", "Murray", ",", "who", "has", "always", "said", "he", "was", "just", "trying", "to", "help", "Michael", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Absolutely not, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "So no sympathy from you towards Conrad Murray?", "question_tokens": ["So", "no", "sympathy", "from", "you", "towards", "Conrad", "Murray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "No sympathy.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "sympathy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Let me ask you, Lavelle, how could that be possible?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "Lavelle", ",", "how", "could", "that", "be", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "You tell me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "tell", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lavelle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Michael Prince, when you heard the now infamous tape of Michael slurring and sounding completely out of it, were you as shocked as everybody else, given that you were working so closely with him?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", "Prince", ",", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "now", "infamous", "tape", "of", "Michael", "slurring", "and", "sounding", "completely", "out", "of", "it", ",", "were", "you", "as", "shocked", "as", "everybody", "else", ",", "given", "that", "you", "were", "working", "so", "closely", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I was shocked to hear it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "shocked", "to", "hear", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Prince", "Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What do you think Michael's legacy should be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "Michael", "'s", "legacy", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Well, Michael's legacy, unequivocally, Piers, is going to be his children.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Michael", "'s", "legacy", ",", "unequivocally", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "going", "to", "be", "his", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}]